- Sometimes you need more than just words on a screen
-有時，您不僅需要屏幕上的單詞
or a verbal description to really bring an idea to life.
或口頭描述，才能真正實現想法。
For example,
例如，
I could try to describe a dream I had last night,
我可以嘗試描述我昨晚的夢，
or better yet, I could just show you.
或者更好的是，我可以向您展示。
So, most of us would jump at the chance
因此，我們大多數人都會有機會以令人印象深
to make our work stand out with impressive visuals,
刻的視覺效果讓我們的作品脫穎而出，
but this can be out of reach if you're not a designer,
但如果您不是設計師，這可能是無法觸及的，
but with Gemini, you can create and transform content
但有了 Gemini，您可以創建和轉換多種
across media types.
媒體類型的內容。
For example, you can build marketing materials
例如，您可以為您
or images for your website,
的網站構建行銷材料或圖像，
you can take a report and turn it into a presentation,
您可以獲取報告並將其轉換為簡報
or you can even create a video with just a prompt.
，甚至只需提示即可創建視頻。
You can do all of this using AI's multimodal capabilities.
您可以使用 AI 的多模式功能來完成所有這些。
This means that you can make a request in one format,
這意味著您可以以一種格式（例如
like an image,
圖像）提出請求，
and get an output in a different format, like a video.
並獲取不同格式的輸出，例如視頻。
For example, you could give Gemini a text prompt
例如，您可以給 Gemini 一個文本提示
and get an image in return, like this.
並獲得像這樣的圖像。
It can also take something like an image
它還可以拍攝像像圖像的東
and turn it into a video like this one.
西並將其轉換為像這樣的視頻。
Hey, wanna see something really cool?
嘿，想看看真的很酷的東西嗎？
It can even take a set of images
它甚至可以拍攝一組圖像
and combine them into something else.
並將它們合併為其他東西。
So, AI provides a whole new way of working,
因此，AI 提供了一種全新的工作方式，
where your ideas and creative vision define the strategy
您的想法和創意願景定義策略，
and AI can instantly turn this into reality.
而 AI 可以立即將這種工作變成現實。
So, what does this mean for you and your work?
那麼，這對您和您的工作意味著什麼？
Well, first, you can gain the ability
好吧，首先，您可以獲得
to generate high-quality images and videos.
生成高質量圖像和視頻的能力。
You can add these easily into any work product
您可以輕鬆地將這些內容添加到任何工作產品
or in your messages to your team,
中，或在向團隊、利
stakeholders, or customers.
益相關者或客戶的消息中添加。
Second, you can expand your ability to create
其次，您可以通過
with instant format transformation.
即時格式轉換來擴展創作能力。
Start with something in a Google Doc, like your messy notes,
從 Google 文件中的內容開始，例如雜亂的筆記，
or a PDF, a spreadsheet, an audio file, or another format,
或 PDF，試算表，音頻文件或其他格式，
and then from there, you can direct AI
然後從那裡，您可以指導 AI 將其
to turn this into a five-minute presentation outline.
轉換為五分鐘的簡報大綱。
Third, Gemini can give you on-demand feedback
第三，Gemini 可以在您創
while you're creating a draft or piece of content.
建草稿或內容時向您提供隨選反饋。
Anytime you want, you can ask Gemini for pointed critiques,
隨時隨地，您可以向 Gemini 提出明確的批評，例如：
like, "Does this presentation clearly explain our proposal?"
「這個演示是否清楚地解釋了我們的建議？」
or, "How might our audience of first-time home buyers
或者，「我們的首次購買家庭觀眾對此影片
respond to this video ad?"
廣告會如何回應？」
Gemini can help you find potential areas for improvement
Gemini 可以幫助您找到可能需要改進的領域
and give you tangible suggestions
，並為您提供有形
for how to refine your work.
的建議，有關如何精進您的工作。
So, how should you use your experience and insights
那麼，您應該如何利用您的經驗和見解
to direct it?
來指導它？
Well, think of AI as your thought partner,
好吧，將 AI 視為您的思想夥伴，而
not your replacement.
不是您的替代人。
Review everything it produces
檢閱它所產生
and make sure it matches your perspective or your brand,
的所有內容，並確保它
and if you're representing something as fact,
與您的觀點或品牌相符，如果您將某些事實呈現為事實，例
like transforming a report into an infographic,
如將報告轉換為信息圖表，
double check that AI got it right.
請仔細檢查 AI 是否正確。
And always exercise your judgment
並始終問自己
by asking yourself if you're using AI
是否以適合情境和受
in a way that's appropriate
眾的方式使用
given the context and the audience.
AI 來執行判斷力。
By the end of this course, you'll be able
在本課程結束時，您將能夠
to use these techniques to quickly prototype,
使用這些技術快速製作原型，創
create engaging content,
建引人入勝
and get feedback and pointers about your work.
的內容，並獲得關於您的工作的反饋和指示。
All right, if you're ready to start using AI
好了，如果你準備好開始使用 AI
to bring your ideas to life,
來實現你的想法，
let's get going.
讓我們開始吧。